One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Punk Hazard Island Central Lake
‒ Zoro's Group ‒
I wonder, could that be a Slime?
Slime?
Indeed. I have read about them in books.
That thing looks exactly like the monsters called Slimes
that appeared in those books.
I was fascinated by what I read!
The monsters called Slimes tend to attack women...
and their body fluids melt the women's clothes!
Truly indecent monsters!
Who would make up
such a ridiculously convenient monster?!
C-C-Could you lend me that book later?
And me!
Hey idiots, take a good look.
Pinky swear!
I dunno if it melts your clothes or whatever, but touching it is probably bad.
The fish are dying because of
the body fluids that have fallen into the lake.
Those things are clusters of poison.
This whole lake will become toxic if we wait too long.
Toxic?
Then what will happen to Samurai-san's torso?
Don't tell me... you're going after it, Sanji-san?!
Of course I'm going!
Blood will be on my hands if I don't!
As a man, this is something I must do!
Sanji-san!
Just do something about the Slimes around us.
What? Around us...
Slimelings! When did they surround us?!
Forgive me, Nami-san.
I'm the best swimmer we've got.
I will return
before any harm befalls your beautiful body!
Please, take care!
Th-This is colder than freezing!
Where is that torso?!
Monet is the only one here.
This is my chance.
If you're looking for Master, he's not here.
I see. Where is he?
Who knows. He's pretty twisted,
so he's probably watching the battle outside.
I've found everything
that I'm going to find on this island...
so I'm planning to leave soon.
I see. It'll be lonely without you.
First, your ability could be helpful for a small task.
Mind coming with me?
Oh, a date? How lovely.
Unsocial as ever, I see.
What is it?
You'll see once we get there.
Fair enough. I was bored anyway.
Is that the bird-lady Usopp was talking about?
Caesar's Lab Main entrance
‒ Luffy's Group ‒
S-Straw Hat's got Master!
Nice going, Luffy!
Damn that bastard!
Straw Hat!
Let go of me, you filth!
No way!
So that's Haki, huh?
Luffy is one hell of a guy!
He's holding onto a Logia user.
Straw Hat! Get away from Master!
We've gotta save Master!
I'm your opponent!
Clutch!
Get outta my way!
With Luffy as strong as he is now,
that guy should be a piece of cake!
We can't be sure, just yet.
The Color of Arms Haki can restrain Logia users, who would normally be untouchable,
but it can't take away their power
the way ocean-energy or Sea Stone can.
We still don't know the true power...
of the Gas Gas Fruit.
Don't get cocky!
Color of Armaments: Hardening!
Rubber...
Bell!
Gas Robe!
What's this?!
It's wrapping around me! I can't get it off!
How long can you hold your breath?
Just inhale it already, and die!
Luffy!
Damn it all!
I've performed experiment after experiment
in order to heighten the deadliness of my gas.
Has he lost his mind?!
He's intentionally breathing in Master's poisonous gas!
He inhaled it all!
He's dead!
I guess poison doesn't affect me much anymore.
Must be because of Magellan.
Magellan?!
The poison-man of Impel Down?
Don't you dare compare me to that Paramecia-user!
Rubber...
Jet Mace!
Master!
That bastard! What did he do to our Master?!
Do not interfere, trash!
T-Trash?!
Did he just call us... trash?!
You must have heard it wrong!
Rubber...
Bring it!
Gatling!
Gastanet!
Luffy!
That's our Master!
Now, time to finish you off.
Awaken, Smileys!
Smileys?
What?! They're starting to move!
Smileys, stick yourselves to Straw Hat!
Jump!
Why are these things listening to Master?!
Luffy, be careful! They're gonna explode!
Luffy!
Blow him to pieces!
Gastanet!
Luffy!
Rubber...
Jet Stamp!
M-Master!
That was one huge explosion!
He escaped from the explosion! That guy sure is fast!
Thank goodness.
S-Straw Hat just...
Is he immortal?!
Alright!
How dare you hurt our Master?!
Get outta my way!
Alright, this time I've got you!
Master!
Robin! Franky! You got anything to keep this guy in?
He's a Logia-user, so tying him up won't work.
Hmmm, is there a barrel or something lying around?
Hey, hold it, Straw Hat!
The Navy's G-5 unit will take him into custody.
And you too!
Prepare yourselves!
Smoker-san! Straw Hat's group have got Caesar!
Straw Hat?
Luffy?
You really underestimated me.
Inside the Laboratory
‒ Law's Group ‒
Law?
Who's there?!
What's wrong?
It looks like you're in pain.
Who's... there?!
It's me.
What... are you...
doing here?!
How many years has it been?
You've grown, Law.
Did you honestly think
he didn't know what you were up to?
We do not trust Caesar.
That is why he went to great lengths to infiltrate Caesar's operations...
using Monet.
I hear you're one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea now.
How mighty you've become.
When did you get here...
Vergo?!
I just arrived.
I happened to be in Dressrosa...
and an S.A.D. tanker was heading here, so I got on it.
Looks like I made the right choice.
What do you mean by that?!
Have I ever harmed you?!
If any harm had been done to us, you would already be dead.
But if you try to keep secrets from adults, you will inevitably be caught, Law.
Then... I'll just have to...
get rid of you!
Oh, and there's one other thing.
You misspoke.
It's Vergo-san.
In Front of the Laboratory - Luffy's Group
What just happened?
I have no idea.
What should we do?!
Tashigi-chan!
That's Vice-Admiral Smoker!
I never thought I'd see the day
when he was beaten unconscious twice!
The three Straw Hats were all beaten too!
Could it have been the Haki of Conquerors?
No way! There couldn't possibly be
that big a gap in their power!
Then what was it?!
He took them all out without lifting a finger!
Serves you right, Navy!
That's the true power of our god of salvation, Master!
Master! Master! Master!
My mighty soldiers!
Put all five of them in chains!
Use Sea Stone on the Devil Fruit users!
You can leave the marine grunts where they are,
and follow me inside the laboratory.
It's dangerous here.
Strange creatures seem to be raining down on us,
but do not worry!
I will make sure our place remains safe!
Yes, Master!
The Cool Brothers seem to have failed me.
Well, there's no helping that.
Fighting Straw Hat and Law
must have been too much for them.
Central Lake - Zoro's Group
I've had enough of this!
I-I-It's poison gas!
My eyes! My eyes!
Wait! I had no eyes in the first place!
Why would you do that?!
You're just some freak with jelly for a body!
More poison gas!
What should we do, Zoro-san?! It spews poison gas!
I just did that, didn't I?!
Try to learn from others, skeleton!
I thought maybe you just had bad luck.
I know! The enemy is jelly!
You should eat and digest them.
No way!
Stop bullying me like that!
I am at least seventy years older than you!
Sorry... Grampa.
Who are you calling Grampa?!
I am still a fit young skel-
What's wrong?!
It's so cold! Sorry, Nami-san.
Could that be...
the Slime's toxin?!
Come on, now!
I hope that the samurai's torso
hasn't been consumed by the toxins!
I've been using
the Color of Perception for a while now, and yet...
He must be quite weak.
His life-signs are getting mixed with the fish,
so I can't tell where he is!
A shark?!
Hey, are you kidding me?!
A-Are you alright?
Hey, what is it? What's going on?!
Hold it right there, damn fish!
Don't eat him, shark!
I-It hurts not! It merely itches!
What the hell?
He's obviously in pain.
It hurts... not!
What if something has happened to Sanji-san?!
Let go of him, damn you!
Now!
Joue Shot!
Joue: Cheek
Alright! The final piece is safe!
With this, the samurai puzzle is completed!
I've gotta hurry and get back...
before the path is gone!
Damn it!
Has the poison spread this much?!
This is bad! I've been cut off without realizing it!
Can Nami-san's muscles do what I need them to?
This will cause her trouble later, but...
This is bad!
The poison has
almost completely spread through the lake!
Sanji-san, hurry!
Blue Walk!
Don't close! Don't close! Don't close!
Sanji-san!
Look at that, he got him!
He really did!
What can I say?
Never before have I been so happy
just to have the body I was born with!
Samurai from the Wano Kingdom
Foxfire Kin'emon
Oh my! Samurai-san, you certainly are big!
You're as tall as me!
I just realized, I have not introduced myself properly!
My name is Kin'emon!
I was born in Kuri, Wano Kingdom!
H-H-Hurry it up!
I'm gonna die here!
Very well! I am most sorry.
Transform!
I'm still cold...
That coat will disappear if he takes it off, right?
Man with the eyebrows,
will you give me your name in return?
I'm Sanji!
And what do you mean by this?!
Just because you've got your body back,
you suddenly want a polite introduction festival?!
You took full advantage when you were helpless...
and spouted countless cheeky rude comments at me!
You haven't forgotten, have you?!
You people are pirates?!
That explains your savagery!
I loathe pirates. They make me vomit!
You're such an annoying bastard!
Just ask us! Say "Please search for my body"!
I refuse to be indebted to a pirate!
I would sooner die than ask for your help!
Alas, I would be defenseless if you left me here,
but if you want to take me with you...
I would not complain.
I have not forgotten!
I will never...
forget what you've done for me!
For as long as I live!
I can never repay this debt!
Also, I never stopped doubting you until you gave me my torso back.
Please, forgive me for that!
I beg of you! I beg of you!
Cut it out, idiot! Raise your head!
A man shouldn't bow so easily!
But... if you had not shown up, I would never have...
Uh, I hate to interrupt, but... Sanji-san...
We do appear to be in the middle of a hopeless crisis.
Look. See?
There's nowhere left to run!
Hey, you guys!
Didn't I tell you to take care of these things?!
We tried but nothing worked. Not our fault.
Exactly.
Don't be so lax, idiots!
I can't let Nami-san's body be hurt!
This body...
This body absolutely must not...
You don't want to give it back, do you?
Of course I don't.
Shall we try igniting them?
Foxfire Kin'emon is my name.
My blade is one that scorches its enemies.
I shall make that creature combust, and thus open a passage for us!
Scorches its enemies? That sounds like magic!
He... cut the flames!
The way is open.
I am coming for you now, Momonosuke!
What the?! We're unharmed!
I'm sure that we were
just engulfed by the flames of that explosion!
K-K-Kin'emon-san... What just happened?
I merely cut the explosion in pieces.
You cut it?!
My Foxfire Style scorches enemies with flames,
and furthermore,
one of its special techniques is to cut flames apart.
There is no fire I cannot cut!
Now then, I shall head for the laboratory to rescue Momonosuke.
Please excuse me!
Hold it!
Your samurai fighting style has caught my interest.
I'll help you save your son.